제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신 주, 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
1976년 목요일
Thursday, 1976
오후 4시 15분
4:15 p.m.
에릭네 지하실
Eric Forman's Basement
게임 룰은 아나콘다야
포커게임의 일종
The game is Anaconda.
에이스, 8, 퀸, 잭, 5, 조커...
Big Ace, Eight Ball, Red Lady,
Jackson, Fiver, Wild Man…
어머, 세상에, 마이클!
Oh my god, Michael!
- 디스코장이 문을 연대
- 어디에?
- They opened up a disco!
- Where at?
케노샤에
In Kenosha.
너 데이빗 보위 엉덩이 바지
입고 가면 되겠다
엉덩이가 꽉끼는 나팔바지
You could wear your
David Bowie butt huggers.
마이클, 그거 짱이겠는데!
Michael, that would be super!
웃고 싶음 웃어, 그거 입으면
내 엉덩이가 얼마나 예뻐보이는데
Laugh if you want, man, but my
butt looks pretty good in those.
야, 너네들 미쳤냐?
디스코장이라고? 웃기지 마
Fine. Are you guys crazy?
I mean, a disco? No way.
글쎄, 춤추러 가는 것도
재밌을 거 같은데
I don’t know, it might be
kinda fun to go dancing.
그럼 가야지
Oh, we could go!
개패잖아, 난 죽을래
I got nothing, I fold.
야, 죽을 거면
가서 팝콘이나 튀겨와
Oh, man, if you're out,
go make some popcorn.
얘도 데리고 가
Take her with you.
디스코가 뭐야?
What is disco?
디스코는 지옥에서 온거야, 알았어?
Disco is from hell, ok?
지옥중에서도 살인자들이
사는 쿨한 곳 말고
And not the cool part of hell
with all the murderers,
사악한 회계사들이 사는
구린 곳 말야
but the lame ass part where
the really bad accountants live.
잠깐만, 너 뭐하는 거야?
Excuse me,
what are you doing?
켈소 카드 보잖아
Looking at Kelso's cards.
- 그건 사기야
- 에릭, 팝콘 어딨는지 모르겠어
- That's cheating.
- Eric! I can't find the popcorn!
야, 음..
Hey, um,
도나, 내 패도 보지 그러냐?
Donna, why don't
you take a little look at my cards,
그럼 내가 자리 뜰 때까지
기다릴 필요 없을 거 아냐
then you won't have to
wait for me to leave.
괜찮아, 어서, 봐봐
No, come on, take a look.
보라니까, 내 패를 봐
이 사기꾼아!
Take a look, tell me what I have,
you cheater!
너 개패잖아!
You got nothing!
맞아, 그리고 난 뻥카칠 거니까
조심해!
Yeah, and I'm gonna bluff,
so watch out!
도나 너 에릭한테
무슨 맘있구나, 맞지?
Donna has stuff for Eric, yes?
무슨 맘이 아냐, 확실한 거지
Not stuff, thing.
도나는 에릭한테 확실히 맘이 있어
Donna has a thing for Eric.
넌 왜 에릭을 좋아하는데?
Why do you have a thing for Eric?
에릭은 재밌는 데다
바보같은 질문도 안 하니까
He makes me laugh, he doesn't
ask me stupid questions.
걘 똑똑한데다가, 알잖아..
He's smart, and, you know…
- 아니, 모르겠는데?
- 나 알아!
- No, I don't know.
- I know!
에릭은 품위가 있으니까!
여자들은 자기가 믿을 수 있는
It is because Eric is noble,
and a woman wants her first love
남자의 품안에서 첫사랑을
만들어 가고 싶어하거든
making to be in the arms
of a man she can trust!
- 페즈?
- 응?
- Fez?
- Yes.
가서 팝콘이나 튀겨라
Go make popcorn.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
싱크, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
번역수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정 (fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
싱크 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x07 That Disco Episode
Nov 08, 1998 on FOX
아빠, 토요일날 제 통행금지시간
좀 연장해 주세요
Dad, I want to talk to you
about my curfew on Saturday.
케노샤에 있는 디스코장에
가기로 했거든요
We're going to a disco in Kenosha.
오, 춤추러 케노샤에 가다니
제법 멀구나!
Ooh, Dancing in Kenosha.
That's quite a drive!
2시까지만 연장해 주심 안돼요?
Can I push my curfew to two?
- 음..
- 아니면 1시 반?
- Mmm…
- Or one thirty?
- 음..
- 아니면 1시? / 그래!
- Mmm…
- Or one? / Done!
그래서
So!
누구랑 갈거냐?
Who's going?
도나요, 뻔하죠
얘네들 데이트 하잖아요
Oh, Donna, I'm sure,
they're practically dating.
기름값 좀 주시면 안돼요?
Can I have some gas money?
데이트? 언제부터?
Dating? Since when?
엄마, 데이트하는 거 아니에요
Mom, we're not dating.
아니긴? 걘 널 좋아해
Why not? She likes you.
고마워요, 엄마
기름값 말인데요..
Thanks mom.
About that gas money…
너한데 관심있다니까
확실해
Well, now, she is interested,
I can tell!
게다가 춤은 여자의 마음을 사로잡는
가장 빠른 방법이지
And dancing is the quickest way
to a gal's heart!
여보, 매키노섬 아발론에
춤추러 다니던 거 기억나요?
Remember, Red, when we used to go
dancing at the Avalon on Mackinaw Island?
아, 매키노요! 그거야 말로 제법 먼데요!
분명히 거리가..
Oh, Mackinaw! Now that's quite a drive!
I bet the mileage is just…
오, 볼라레! 오, 오!
깐따레! 오~
Oh, oh! Volare! Oh!
Cantare! Oh, oh!
네가 무슨 짓을 했는지 알겠냐?
You see what you did?
네 엄마 병이 다시 도졌잖아!
You got your mother started!
기가 막힌다, 니네들 꼬임에
우리가 다같이 디스코장을 간다니
Man, I can't believe you and Jackie
are dragging everybody to that disco.
정말 슬퍼
It’s so sad.
난 케노샤 여자애들 꼬시러 가는거야
No, I'm just going to meet
Kenosha chicks.
재키랑은 끝낼 거야
I'm Breaking up with Jackie.
그럼 키 큰 애로 꼬셔!
Oh, get a tall chick!
너랑 재키 같이 있는 거 보면
되게 우스워
Because you and Jackie
look so silly together!
빈병이랑 알루미늄 캔은 이게 다야
Ok, that's all the deposit
bottles and the aluminum cans.
이 정도면 최소한
We gotta have at least…
1불 50센트 어치 기름 넣겠다
a dollar fifteen worth of gas.
가자, 우리 아빠가
빈병 왕창 모아 놓으셨어
Come on.
My dad's got a ton of empties.
바보같은 디스코장 가는데
돈을 낭비하다니 말도 안돼요
Man, I can't believe they're gonna waste
all their money on a stupid disco
그 돈이면 진짜 왕장
큰 걸로 살수 있는데..
when they could buy a really big bag…
카라멜이요
Of caramels!
디스코장에 안 갈거냐?
Not going to that disco, huh?
네
No.
짜증나는 음악이나 듣는
허접한 인간들은 제 취향 아니에요
Phony people listening to crappy music
does not sound like my kinda time.
너 춤 못추는구나, 그렇지?
You can't dance, can you?
춤 출줄 알아요
I can dance.
아닐껄
Oh, I don't think so, pal.
안다니까요
I can dance.
한발도 못뗄껄
Not one step.
맞아요, 한발도 못떼요
You're right, not one step.
그럼 문제가 있구나, 얘야
Well, then you got a problem, son.
왜냐면 여자들은 춤추고 싶어하거든
‘cause women wanna dance.
항상 춤추고 싶어하지
They always wanna dance.
항상
Always.
왜요?
Why?
왜냐면 말이지
’Cause.
남자 앞에 바싹 달라붙어서
몸을 흔들어 댈 수 있으니까
They get close and wiggle their
bodies around in front of a man
안전한 분위기 속에서 말이다
in a safe atmosphere.
전 사람들 있는데서
흔들고 싶지 않아요
See, I don't really wanna
wiggle around in public.
물론 그렇겠지
넌 남자니까
Well, of course not.
You're a man.
그래도 넌 춤을 배워야 돼
My point is,
you're going to have to learn.
안 그러면 나중에는 말이다
Otherwise later on in life,
너 혼자서 흔들고 있게 될거야
you're gonna be
wiggling all by yourself.
너만 배우고 싶다면
Now if you want,
내가 도와줄 수 있다
I can help you out.
좋아, 아주 잘했어
다시 해보자, 알겠지? 시작
Ok, now, that was good.
Ok, let's try it again. Ok? Now.
왼발, 오른발, 왼발
돌고 찍고, 좋아
Left, right, left, turn and step. Ok.
음악을 못 쫓아 가겠어요, 아줌마
I can't keep up with music,
Mrs. Forman.
너무 낙심하지 말자꾸나
Now, lets not get discouraged!
좋아, 음악은 끄자!
All right. I am just gonna
turn this music off!
이제 날 따라해 봐
괜찮아, 넌 할 수 있어
Now! You follow me.
Ok. You can do this. Ok.
왼발
Left,
오른발
right,
왼발
left,
돌고
turn
찍고!
and step!
아야.. 아냐, 아냐!
Ooh…no! No! No!
네 발을 보지 말고 나를 봐
Look at me, not at your feet.
자, 이제 나한테 팔을 둘러 봐
Ok, you know what, now, now,
put your arm around me.
그래, 약간 아래로
손을 내 허리부분에 놔
Yeah, a little bit lower, put your
hand in the small of my back.
날 이끌수 있을 것 같니?
You feel how you can guide me?
- 오, 예..
- 좋아, 좋아
- Oh! Yeah…
- Ok, ok.
왼발, 오른..
네가 리드하고 있어!
Left, r…
you're leading!
좋아, 이제 어디로 이동할 건지
네 손으로 나한테 알려줘, 으흥
Ok, now. Tell me where
to move with your hands. Uh-huh.
왼발
Left,
오른발
right,
왼발
left,
돌고, 으흠, 좋아
돌 때 눈을 맞추고, 좋아, 그 다음..
turn, uh-huh, ok,
eye contact in the turn, ok, ok, and…
기울이고!
dip!
괜찮아
Ok,
다시 한번만 해보자
well now let's just do it again.
계세요? 아무도 없어요?
Hello! Anybody home?
보온병 돌려주러 왔어요
I'm bringing back your thermos!
으흥, 손을 거기에 두고
오, 완벽해!
Ouh, put your hand there.
Oh, that is perfect!
너 아저씨보다 잘 하는구나!
You are better than Red!
온 몸이 녹초가 됐구나
땀으로 범벅이 됐어
Oh, I am exhausted!
That is sweaty work!
아줌마, 오늘 일은 우리 둘사이
비밀로 했음 좋겠어요
Mrs. Forman,
I'd really appreciate it
if maybe we didn't tell anybody
what we were doing here.
비밀로 할께
Oh, mum is the word!
내일 학교 끝나고 보자, 괜찮지?
Tomorrow after school, okay?
감사합니다
Thanks.
그리고 스티븐?
And Steven?
아주 잘 하더구나
You were good.
좋아, 생각해 봤는데
Ok, I thought about it.
나도 디스코장에 갈거야
And I'm going to the disco!
혹시 로큰롤을 약간 섞어서
틀어줄지도 모르잖아
Just on the off chance.. they
might mix up a little rock ‘n roll, man.
그래?
Yeah?
근데 나 할 말이 있어
Well, I have something to say.
오늘 쇼핑하러 갔다가
I went to the mall today,
새 신발을 한 켤레 샀는데
and I bought a…
pair of new shoes,
내 구두가 디스코장에서
젤로 멋질거야!
and they're the coolest
kicks in the cave!
인제 켈소는 그만 줘라
아주 맛이 갔구만!
So, no more for Kelso,
he's toasted!
너희들이 토스트 만들어 주면
나도 먹고 싶어
I would like some toast
if you are making some.
아니면 아무 음식이나 괜찮아
나 배고파 죽겠어!
Or food of any kind would
be good. I am starving!
어디서 읽었는데 인도에서는
단식수행하는 사람들도 있다더라
Oh, I read somewhere there are
these people in India who fast, Yeah!
게다가 그 사람들 정신력이
너무 대단해서
And their minds are so advanced,
생각만으로도 자기 자신을
죽게 할 수 있대
they could actually think
themselves to death, man!
우와
Whoa.
내가 지금 그러고 있는게
아녔으면 좋겠다
I hope I'm not doing that right now.
내 정신은 항상 난 알지도
못하는 짓을 저지르고 있거든
My mind's always doing things
that I don't even know about!
우린 이 아래서 맨날 대단한
일들을 많이 생각하는데 말야
Man, we always think of
so many brilliant things down here,
나중에는 하나도 생각이 안 나더라
but then later I can't
remember any of them!
정말 기똥찬데 말야
I mean, they're brilliant man!
누구 얼른 가서 토스트 만들어 와
Someone go make toast right now.
야, 우리 대화를 녹음하는 거야
Hey, we should record
our conversation, man!
그래! 그런 다음
다시 듣고 받아 적는거야
Yeah! Then we could play
it back and write it down!
전국 풍자가협회의 작가들도
그런 식으로 하는게 틀림없어
I'll bet that's how the writers
at National Lampoon do it!
맞아, 나도 어디서 읽었는데
프랑스에도 어떤 사람들이 있다더라
Yeah, well, I read somewhere that
there's these people in France!
그 사람들이 뭘 하는데?
What do they do?
그 사람들 정말 믿기지 않는 게
You see, they are incredibly…
프랑스말을 한대!
French!
봐, 정말 대단하잖아!
녹음기 가져와야겠다!
See, that's brilliant, man!
I'm getting the tape recorder!
내 토스트 어딨어, 이 바보들아?
Where's my toast, you idiots?
에릭
Eric!
네, 아빠
Yeah, dad.
토요일 날 밤에
기름값 필요한 거 안다
Listen, I know you need
gas money for Saturday night,
그래서 말인데 네가 집안일을 몇가지
더 하겠다면 내가 10달러 주마
so if you're willing to do a few extra
chores, I'll uh, pay you ten dollars.
당연히 해야죠
Sure I can do that.
그럼, 차고를 쓸고
배수로 낙엽을 청소하고
Now, I need you to sweep the garage,
clean the leaves out of the gutters,
세탁물 찾아오고
그리고 찬장 선반을 고정시켜라
pick up the dry cleaning,
and uh, fix that shelf in the pantry.
시킨 거 나한테 다시 말해봐
Now, run that back to me.
네, 선반 고정하기, 차고 쓸기
낙엽 찾아오기..
Oh, kay, fix the shelf, sweep
the garage, pick up the leaves…
세탁물
Dry cleaning.
맞아요
Yeah.
배수로
The gutters.
배수로 고정하기
Fix the gutters.
청소, 배수로 청소하라고
Clean, clean the gutters.
배수로 청소하기, 선반 고정하기
낙엽 쓸기요
Clean out the gutters,
fix the shelf, sweep the leaves.
차고
The garage.
차고 고정하기
Fix the garage.
- 차고는 쓸어
- 쓸어야죠
- Sweep it.
- Sweep.
제대로 일 못하면 10달러 안 줄거다
Listen, I'm not gonna pay you
ten dollars for nothing!
차고 쓸기, 세탁물 찾아오기
배수로 청소하기, 선반 고정하기요
Sweep the garage, pick up the cleaning,
clean up the gutters, fix the shelf.
그걸 다 하면 기름값을 주마
Do that, and you got
yourself gas money.
낙엽도 어떻게 하라고
하지 않으셨어요?
Didn't you say
something about leaves?
낙엽은 배수로 안에 있잖아
They're in the gutters.
맞아요, 찾아와야죠
Right. Pick 'em up.
아니, 청소해야죠
전.. 토스트 만들 거예요
Clean 'em up!
I…gotta make toast.
오, 이런, 여보
Aw, jeez, Midge.
키티랑 저 녀석 또 시작이로군
Kitty and that boy are at it again.
너 냄새 되게 좋다
뭐 했어?
You smell great.
What'd you do?
목욕했어
I took a bath.
내내 네 생각 했어
I was thinking of you the whole time.
- 샤워하면서 나도 그랬어
- 뭐? / 아냐
Yeah, you know I do the same thing
in the shower. / What? / Nothing.
사진 찍자, 준비됐다
스티븐 좀 가까이 서렴
Oh, let's take some pictures!
I'm ready, Steven get in closer.
자, 다같이 치~즈!
Ok, let's all smush together!
크게 웃어! 좋아! 잘했다!
Ok, big smiles! Nice! Ok!
이제, 여자애들
Now, girls,
어디 얼마나 예쁜가 보자
웃어, 잘했다!
look how pretty, smile, nice!
이제, 남자애들
오, 너무 잘 생겼구나!
Now boys, oh, so handsome!
- 자, 이제..
- 엄마, 제가 엄마 사진 찍어드릴께요
Ok, now. One, two.. / Hey, mom,
why don't I take a picture of you?
아냐, 아냐
괜찮아, 늦겠다 얼른 가렴
No, no, no, no.
Ok, you'll be late, bye now!
- 아줌마가 최고예요
- 확실히 보여주고 오렴, 얘야
- You're the best.
- Oh, you go get them, Tiger.
키티, 당신 조언이 필요해요
Kitty, I need your advice.
물론이죠, 뭔데요?
Well, sure, what is it?
결혼한 친구가 있는데요
I have this married friend.
자기보다 훨씬 어린 남자에게 끌려서
자기 인생을 내던지려고 해요
And she's about to
throw everything away
because she's attracted
to a much younger man.
스텔라 얘기죠?
It's Stella!
아뇨
No!
스텔라가 작업중인 거
저도 알아요!
Oh, I knew that Stella was
open for business!
스텔라 아니에요
It's not Stella!
그럼 제가 아는 사람인가요?
Well, do I know her?
네, 아주 잘 알죠
Yes, very well.
이런, 미지!
Oh, Midge!
밥도 알아요?
Does Bob know?
네, 그이는 어찌 할 바를
모르고 있어요
Yeah, and he doesn't
know what to do!
키티, 나도 어떡해야 될지
모르겠고요
Kitty, I don't know what to do!
미지, 잘 들어요
Midge, listen.
당신 친구는 자기가 상처입히게 될
모든 사람들을 생각해야 될 거예요
I think your friend should think about
all of the people she's gonna hurt.
그리고 누가 됐든
알고 싶지도 않지만
And tell this younger man whoever
he is, I don't wanna know,
that it has to stop.
그 아이에게도 그만두라고
말해야 되구요
고마워요
Thank you.
제 친구가 당신 충고를
받아들였으면 좋겠어요
I just hope my friend
takes your advice.
분명히 그럴 거라고 믿어요
I'm sure your friend will.
흠.. 영계란 말이지
Hmm. Younger man.
어떤 느낌일지 궁금하네
Wonder what that's like.
재키, 어디 갔었어?
Jackie, where'd you go?
네 입에다가 물릴 것 찾으러 갔었어
I had to get something
for you to bite on,
사람들한테 네가 발작하는
중이라고 말했거든
cause I told everyone you
were having a seizure!
디스코 음악은 언제 틀어주는 거야?
When do they play
the disco music?
이게 디스코 음악이야
This is disco music.
아냐, 이건 삼바야
No, no. This is samba.
페즈, 이게 디스코란다
쓰레기지
Fez, it's disco, man.
It's crap!
우와, 이 쓰레기 맘에 드는데
Whoa, I think I like this crap!
이리와, 재키!
한바퀴 돌러 가자!
Come, Jackie! Let's get down!
아냐, 난 좀 피곤해
No, I think I'm a little tired.
튕기지 말고
Don't resist me mama.
신나게 놀아 보자
It's boogie time!
너 방금 데이트 상대를 뺏긴 것 같다?
I think you just lost your date!
뭐 괜찮아
재키랑 나는 이제 끝났으니까
Yeah, well it's cool
‘cause Jackie and I are history!
재키가 보기보다 가벼운가 봐
She must not weigh that much.
재키가 지금 저 자식
엉덩이 만지는 거야?
Is she touching his ass?
메렝게다! / 우악!
카리브해 춤곡
- Listen, Merengue!
- Whoo!
페즈, 너 미쳤구나!
Fez, you're crazy!
우와, 쟤네 정말 잘 춘다
Wow, they are really good!
저딴 식으로 추고 싶냐?
Yeah, if you wanna
dance that way!
난 저렇게 추는 게 좋아
I would love to dance that way!
춤 출래?
You wanna dance?
좋아!
Sure!
춤 좀 추는데
You dance.
너한테 이런 재주가 있는 줄 몰랐어
This is a side of you
I've never seen.
사실은 처음 춰보는 거야
Yeah. Actually,
you're my first dance.
내가 네 첫상대라고?
I'm your first?
이거 영광이군
I'm honored.
이거 멋진데
This is nice.
그래
Mmm-hmm.
도나, 너한테 키스하고 싶어졌어
Donna, man,
I feel like I wanna kiss you.
싫으면 넌 안해도 돼
You don't have to kiss me back
if you don't want.
농담 아냐
I'm not kidding.
입 닥치고 춤이나 춰
Shut up and dance.
페즈, 너 기가 막히게 춤 잘 추더라
Fez, you are an amazing dancer!
재키, 내가 춤을 잘 추는
비결은 바로 너야
Actually Jackie,
you are the reason I am amazing.
남자는 춤을 출 때
You see, when a man dances,
그 여자를 아름다운 꽃처럼
보이게 해야 돼
he should display the woman
to the room like a beautiful flower.
오, 페즈!
Oh, Fez!
- 마이클
- 야! 너, 더는 못 참아
- Michael!
- Alright, pal, that's it!
나랑 지금 당장 한판 붙자!
It's you and me, right here, right now!
- 왜 우리 사이에 끼어드는데?
- 재키는 내 여자친구야, 페즈
Why did you have to interrupt us?
Jackie is my girl, Fez.
쟤랑 끝낼 거라고 했잖아!
But you are breaking up with her!
그딴 소리를 어디서 들었어?
Where do you even get that stuff?
알았어, 나 이제 도망갈 거야
Ok, I'll be running away now.
마이클, 마..
Michael, M…
마이클!
Michael!
마이클, 페즈 잘못이 아냐
Michael, it's not his fault!
넌 나하고 어떻게
춤춰야 되는지도 모르잖아
You just don't know
how to dance with me!
내가 너랑 춤추는 법을 모른다고
딴 놈한테 가버리는 거야?
I don't know how to danceu,
so you just take off with some other guy?
알았어, 마이클, 미안해
내가 잘못했어
I know, Michael, I'm sorry,
I was wrong.
그치만 난 한송이 꽃처럼
보이고 싶었던 것 뿐이야
But all I wanted to be was
displayed like a flower.
넌 내 꽃이란 거 알잖아
You know that you are my flower.
너무 아름답지
That is so beautiful.
나 좀 내려줘
Put me down.
오, 마이클!
Oh, Michael!
야, 나 지금 퇴장해야 돼
Ok, I'm passing out, now.
어~흠
Ah-hem.
그래, 밥
Ok, Bob.
- 무슨 일인가?
- 그냥 좀.. 궁금해서
- What is it?
- Oh, just uh, curious.
그 하이드라는 아이
어떤 녀석인가?
What's the word on that Hyde kid?
스티븐? 반항기가 좀 있지
Steven? Oh, he's a little rebellious.
약간만 바로잡아 주면 돼
He just needs some direction.
벌써 사고를 치고 있다네, 레드
Apparently, he's getting it, Red.
내가 자네 거실로
들어가려는 데 말야
I uh, I kinda walked into
your living room and,
그 놈하고 키티가 거기서
어떤 도발적 포옹을 하고 있더라고
he and Kitty were in, some sort of,
provocative embrace.
내 생각엔 그 놈이 자네 부인한테
수작거는 거 같았어
I think he's puttin'
the moves on your wife.
오, 이런
Oh, my god.
그 놈을 죽여버리겠어
Now I've gotta kill him.
자네 사슴 사냥 총 좀
가져다 주게, 밥
Get your deer rifle, Bob.
진정해, 레드, 나..
내가 잘못 본 걸 수도 있어
Hold on, Red, I, I, I,
I could've been mistaken!
자네가 봤으니 확실해!
총이나 갖다줘
You know what you saw!
Get the damn gun.
어쩌면 키티 목에
음식이나 뭐가 걸렸었을거야
Maybe she was, uh, choking, on,
you know, on some food or something.
그건 말도 안돼
I can't take that chance.
남자로서 내가
어떻게 해야 되겠나?
What choice do I have as a man?
진정해, 레드
아마 춤추고 있던 걸 수도 있어
Come on, Red. Uh,
they could've been dancing!
이런, 그 아이한테 춤을
가르쳐주고 있었던 게 분명해
Jeez, I'm sure she was
teaching him dancing,
다같이 디스코장에 가지 않았나!
‘cause they're all going to that disco!
오
Oh.
춤을 췄다고?
Dancing, huh?
그래
Yeah.
이런 밥
그거 상당히 논리적이군
Jeez, Bob.
That would be downright logical.
그 녀석을 안쏘길 잘 했어
Good thing I didn't shoot him.
하이드, 디스코 음악에 대한
네 생각이 맞았어
Hyde, you were right
about disco music.
그건 악마야
It is evil.
그 고동치는 리듬때문에
내가 나쁜 짓을 했어
Its pulsing rythm made
me do a bad thing.
그래, 나도 마찬가지야
Yeah, well, me too.
켈소는 내 친군데
걔 여자친구를 뺏을 순 없지
Kelso is my friend,
I cannot take his woman.
넌 좋은 녀석이야, 페즈
You're a good guy, Fez.
사실 뺏을 수 있었는데
안 뺏은 거야
Actually, I could take his woman,
but I won't.
일어나, 집에 가자
Come on, I'll walk you home.
- 나중에 보자
- 또 보자
- See you guys.
- See you.
잘 자
Good night.
하이드가 춤을 추다니
정말 놀랬어
Hey, uh, Hyde dancing,
what a surprise!
그래! 누가 알았겠어?
Yeah! Who knew?
맞아, 너 아주 즐거운 것 같더라
Yeah. You looked like you were
having a pretty good time.
그래, 알잖아, 디스코의 열기
지금은 좀 나아졌어
Yeah, well, you know, disco fever.
You catch it. But I'm better now.
정말이지.. 묘한 밤이었어
Wow. What a, what a weird night.
너 켈소 신발 봤지? / 그래
Hey, did you see
Kelso's shoes? / Yeah.
켈소가 똑같은 신발 신은
여자애 봤을 때 기억나?
Remember when he saw that girl
wearing the same shoes?
맞아! 정말 너무 슬프더라
Oh, yes! That was, actually,
it was pretty sad.
그래
Yeah, it was.
우리가 리오그란데 강 건너던 밤 생각나?
ABBA 'Fernando'의 가사
Hey, um…do you recall that night
we crossed the Rio Grande?
뭐?
What?
당신의 눈을 보면 알 수 있어요
I can see it in your eyes.
무슨 소리 하는 거야?
What are you talking about?
♪ 이 땅의 자유를 위해
당신이 얼마나 자랑스럽게 싸웠는지 ♪
♪ How proud you would’ve fought
for freedom in this land… ♪
입다물어, 그만, 그만해. 쉿!
♪ 그날밤 하늘엔 뭔가 있었어요 ♪
Shut up, don't! Don't! Don't, shhh!
♪ There was something in the air that night! ♪
♪ 별들이 밝게 빛났죠 ♪
♪ The stars were bright! ♪
♪ 페르난도 ♪
♪ Fernando! ♪
미안해, 난 디스코 음악이 싫어
I'm sorry. I hate dance music.
그럼, 왜 갔어?
Then, why'd you go?
널 좋아하니까
I like you.
그러니까..
날 좋아하는 것 뿐이야?
So…you're in like with me?
도나, 난.. 널..
Donna, I'm…I'm in…
나 춤 못 춰
I can't dance.
배워
You'll learn.
♪ 그날밤 하늘엔 뭔가 있었어요 ♪
♪ There was something
in the air that night! ♪
♪ 별들이 밝게 빛났죠 ♪
도나, 다시 키스하고 싶어
♪ The stars were bright… ♪
Donna, I really wanna kiss you again.
♪ 페르난도 ♪
입닥치고 춤이나 춰!
♪ Fernando! ♪
Shut up and dance!
♪ 우리 둘을 위해서 빛나고 있었어요 ♪
♪ They were shining there
for you and me ♪
♪ 그리고 자유를 위해 ♪
♪ and liberty… ♪
♪ 페르난도 ♪
♪ Fernando! ♪
♪ 우리가 질 거라고
생각한 적은 없지만 ♪
♪ Though I never thought
that we could lose, ♪
♪ 후회는 없어요 ♪
♪ There's no regret, ♪
♪ 다시 똑같이 해야 한다고 해도 ♪
♪ If I had to do the same again… ♪
♪ 난 할거에요, 내 친구, 페르난도 ♪
♪ I would, my friend, Fernando! ♪
♪ 다시 똑같이 해야 한다고 해도 ♪
♪ If I had to do the same again… ♪
♪ 난 할거에요, 내 친구, 페르난도 ♪
♪ I would, my friend, Fernando! ♪
내말은 지구가 일종의 농장이라는 거야
I'm saying, the earth is a farm
- 정말 대단해
- 우린 모두 농장에 있는 거지
- That's brilliant
- We're all on a farm…
외계인들이 세운 농장말야!
그리고 우린 가축이야!
a farm put here by aliens man!
And we're the cattle!
우린 가축이라고! 음머!
We're cattle! Moo!
정부는 그걸 알아
저밖에 있다고
And the government knows it,
it's out there, man!
뭐가?
What is?
진실말야
The truth.
무슨 소리하는 거야?
What are you saying?
저밖에 있는게 진실이야!
Out there is the truth!
진실은 저밖에 있어!
The truth is out there, man!
정말 대단해요!
That's seriously brilliant!
봤지? 너희들 전부 바보야!
See, you are all stupid!
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24